Guide to the John W. Shenk Papers, 1900-1935
Department of Special Collections
- CORRESPONDENCE
  - H - GENERAL FILE. (I) (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Henshall. R. P., '27
    - Hermosa Beach Chamber Of Commerce., '14
    - Hermosa Beach Water Corporation., '20; (2)
    - [Hervey, William Rhodes]., '10
    - Hettman, Walter E., '33
    - HEWITT, LESLIE R., nd, '08-'34; (17) (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Hewitt, McCormick, & Crump., '27
  - H - GENERAL FILE. (II) (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Hibbard, Oley., '30
    - Ancient Order Of Hibernians., '22
    - Hickox, Ross T., '24-'34; (4)
    - Hicks, John J., '13
    - Higgins, George D., '31; (3)
    - Hill, A. G., '33
    - Hill, A. J., '26-'33; (4)
    - Hill, John J., '25-'27
    - Hill, Robert G., '23-'24; (4)
    - Hill, Morgan & Bledsoe., nd
    - Hillman, C. D., '20
    - Himble, Adelaide L., nd
    - [Hines, William]., '28
    - Hinshaw, E. H., '14
    - Hjelm, Gustav B., '20; (3)
    - Hoak, E. K., '24
    - Hobday, Robert D., '24-'25; (5)
    - Hockensmith, F. L., '26
    - Hodel & Dewar., '21
    - Hodel, George., '24; (2)
    - Hodge, Virginia, '35
    - Hodghead, Beverly L., '07-'24; (4)
      See also Bar Association Of San Francisco.
    - Hoffman, John W., '24-'33; (5)
    - Hoffman, William., '14; (2)
    - Holbrook, Merrill &Stetson., '14
    - Holland, William Meredith (1875 -)., '22
    - Hollingsworth, A. W., '27-'31; (4)
    - Hollywood High School Debating Squad., '29
    - Hollzer, Harry A. (1880 -)., '26-'31; (9)
      See also JUDICIAL COUNCIL.
    - Holohan, James B., '31
    - Holston, A. R., '22; (2)
    - Hood, Van Lee., '31
    - Hooper, George A., '31; (2)
    - Hotel Senator., '29
    - Hough, Harry., '22
    - Houser, Frederick W., '14-'32; (3)
    - HOWE, LOUIS MCH., '33 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Hrefener, Edward W., '27
    - Hubbard, William P., '35
    - Huff, C. C., '26
    - Huff, D. Eyman., '23
    - Huff, William, '23
    - Hughes, Herbert V. Jr., '32
    - Hughes, Thomas W. (1858 -)., '22
    - Huguley, J. B., '26
    - Huguley, Margret T., '27-'28
    - Hugunin, Harry L., '25
    - Humphrey, William F., '30
    - Hunphreys, William M., '20-'34; (3)
    - Hunsaker, Britt, and Cosgrove., '25
    - Hunsaker, William J., '10-'31; (3)
    - Hunter, Ben S., '24
    - Hunter, Robert G., '24
    - Hunter, Mrs. W. R., '07
    - Huntsberger, Glen E., '27
    - Hupert, Mrs. C., '23
    - Hutchins, H. B., '07
  - I - GENERAL FILE. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Iglesias, Santiago., '33
    - Imperial County, California. Auditor., '22
    - Clerk., '24
    - Imperial County. Republican Central Committee., `08
    - Imperial Irrigation District., `22
    - Imperial Valley Abstract Title and Trust Co., `08; (2)
    - Imperial Valley Farm Association., `26-`27; (6) (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Ingraham, Everett L., `36; (2)
    - Insley, Harry E., `24
    - International Theosophical Headquarters., `27
    - IRELAND, IN RE ESTATE OF., `24-`25 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Irwin, Robert R., nd, `23
  - J - GENERAL FILE. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Jacks, Lile T., `28-`31
    - Jackson, Grant., `20-`24; (3)
    - Jade Tree Studios., `23
    - James, Floyd R., `26-`28
    - James, Henry N., `25-`26
    - James, L. A., `24
    - James, William P. (1870 -).
    - Jameson, H. G., `25
    - Jameson, Robert H., nd
    - Janss, Peter., `23; (2)
    - Jeffers, Frank A., `14
    - Jeffries, John., nd
      See also ANONA GOLD MINING AND MILLING CO.
    - Jewell, A. C., `33
    - The Jewish Times, Inc., `20
    - Johnson, C. B., `14
    - Johnson, Erik., `31
    - Johnson, G. G., `22
    - Johnson, Hiram W. (1866 -)., `36; (2)
    - Johnson, Walter Perry., `27-28
    - Johnston, Charles H., `24
    - Johnstone, W. A., `27
    - Joint Civic Committee., `14
    - Jonathan Club., nd, `22-`30; (22)
    - Jones, Carl Power., `35; (2)
    - Jones, E. Casey., `23
    - Jones, Frances. (Mrs. Carl Power), nd
    - Jones, Griffith., `24-`26; (3)
    - Jones, Johnstone., `14
    - Jones, Jonah Jr. (1901 -)., `24
    - Jones, Leila., `06
    - Jones, Mattison B. (1869 -)., `24-`31; (3)
    - Joplin, Jo. S., `25
    - Jordan, Frank C., `24-`31; (4)
    - Jordan, Wayne E., `31
    - Judd, Albert E., nd, `29-`31; (7)
    - Judd, Leila E., nd
    - Judicial Council of California., nd, `26-`34; (22)
  - K - GENERAL FILE. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Kahn's $15 Suit Store., `11
    - Kalt, E. E. R., `30
    - Karr, Frank., `23
    - Keetch, Arthur., `14-`29; (3)
    - Keller, Henry C., `13
    - Kelley, W. P., `11
    - Kellogg, Frederick., `23
    - Kelso, Ivan., `35
    - Kendrick, A. V.
    - Kennedy, Vincent D., `29-`30; (3)
    - Kerns, S. M., `23
    - Kerr, W. M., `24
    - Charles H. Kewell Company., `31
    - Keyes, Asa., `24; (2)
    - Kidd, Herbert W., `23
    - Kiesling, Henry., `14-`24
    - Kiggens, Harold S., `24
    - Kincaid, Clarence Leslie (1898 -)., `31-`34; (6)
    - King, John F., nd, `24-`35; (3)
    - Kingham, Daisy., `31
    - Kirby, Benjamin., `25
    - Kirby, E. N., `22
    - Kirby, Jesse L., `33-`35; (3)
    - Kirkwood, Marion Rice (1887 -)., `24-`25
    - Kittrelle, Richard., `20
    - Kleinsmid, Rufus Bernard von (1875 -)., `24-`30
    - Kling, David G., `27-`33
    - Knapp, E. H., `22
    - Knights Commander Of the Court Of Honor., `23
    - Knights Of Columbus., `23-`31
    - Knights Templar, Pasadena Commandery No. 31., nd, `20-`23; (9)
    - Kodani, Mrs. Kim., nd
    - Koebig, A. H., `24-`26
    - [Koford, Joseph S.], `28
    - Kohler, Jean Fuller., `22; (3)
    - Kohler, Mary Conway., `29
    - Kreidler, Carl Waldemar., `20-`22; (5)
    - Krempel, Christian.
    - Krowl, William V., `24
    - Kruse, Fred H., `32
  - L - GENERAL FILE. (I) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Lamport, Harry B., `24
    - Lampton, L. E., `23
    - Lande, Hannah T., `27
    - Langdon, William H., `26
    - Lantz, Charles., `20
    - LaPlante, William., `31
    - LaTourrette, Clinton., nd
    - LaTourrette, Elizabeth., `28
    - Launder, William H., `23
    - Lavine, Morris., `24-`35; (7)
    - Lawler, Oscar (1875 -)., `19
    - Lawlor, William Patrick (1854 - 1927)., `25
    - Lawrence, R. M., `31
    - Lawyers Club Of Los Angeles., `32
    - Lawyers Co-Operative Publishing Company., `34-`35; (3)
    - [Layng, John R.], `11; (2)
    - League Of Nations Association. Northern California Branch., nd
    - Lee, Bradner W. Jr., `32-`33; (3)
    - Lee, Henry M., `31
    - Lees, Anna C., `25
    - Legal Briefing Service., `35
    - Legerton, Curtis C., `24; (3)
    - Lehman, Joseph A., `22
    - Lekinetz, C. M., `20
    - Lemmon, Dal M., `32
    - [Lennon, Thomas J. (1866 - 1926).], (2)
    - John W. Leonard Corporation., nd
    - Charles Levy & Son., `07
    - Lewinson, Joseph L., `31
    - Lewis Publishing Company., `26
    - M. H. Lewis and Company., `29
    - Lewis, Mrs. W. G., `23
    - Lewis, William Draper (1867 -).
    - Lichtenberger, H. C., `31
    - [Lieberman, Jacob Julius.], nd
    - Lieberman, Louis., `26; (4)
    - Lincoln, Walter Gould., `24
    - Lincoln Club., nd, `22-`35; (8)
    - Lincoln Mortgage Company Of California., `24-`27; (4)
    - Lindenbaum, Isidore., `33
    - Lindsay, Alexander Jr., `26
    - Linhares, John.
      See SHENK PROPERTIES.
    - Linn, Roy A., `24-`31; (3)
    - Lion's Club Of Los Angeles., `27
    - Lion's Club Of Oakland., `24
    - Lippincott, J. B., `27
    - Lissner, Louis M., `24
    - Lissner, Meyer (1871 -)., `13-`24; (4)
    - Lister, Henry B., `28
    - The Literary Digest., `22; (2)
    - Literary Guild Of America., `31-`33
    - Little, Walter J., `27-`29
    - Lloyd, J. K., `06
  - L - GENERAL FILE. (II) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Lobdell, J. Karl., `22-`23; (4)
    - Locke, Charles Edward (1874 -)., `20
    - Locke, William J., `26
    - Locklin, C. B., `31; (3)
    - Loewenthal, Lissner, Roth & Gunter., `28
    - Loewenthal, Max., `24
    - Logie, John H., `22
    - Lones, C. E., `23
    - Long, Oscar Fitzalan (1852 -)., `24
    - Long Beach Bar Association.
    - Lopez, May., `24
    - Lorenz Agencies, Inc., `28
    - Los Altos Chamber Of Commerce., `31
    - Los Altos Golf and Country Club., `25-`30; (4)
    - Los Angeles Bar Association., nd, '20-'35; (14)
    - Los Angeles Central Labor Council., '23-'32
    - Los Angeles Citizens' Committee., '11
    - Los Angeles, City Of.
      - Assessor., '13
      - Board Of Freeholders., '23
      - Board Of Public Works., '10; (2)
      - Bureau Of Power and Light., '23
      - Bureau Of Water Supply., '29
      - Clerk., '11-'20
      - Harbor Department., '22
      - Inspector Of Buildings., '11
    - Los Angeles City Attorneys' Association., nd
    - Los Angeles Chamber Of Commerce., '13
    - Los Angeles Citizens' Judiciary League., nd
    - Los Angeles College Of Law., '29
    - Los Angeles Co-Operative Club., '26
    - Los Angeles, County Of.
      - Grand Jury., '24
      - Registrar Of Voters., '24
      - Sheriff., '34
      - Superior Courts., '20-'24
    - Los Angeles County Employees' Association., '20-'22; (3)
    - Los Angeles County Law Library., '20-'24; (4)
    - Los Angeles, Crime Commission Of., '23; (3)
    - Los Angeles Developers., '25
    - Los Angeles Examiner., '22-'26; (4)
    - Los Angeles Evening Express., '19
    - Los Angeles Good Government Fund., '10; (2)
    - Los Angeles Hebrew Club., '14
    - Los Angeles Investment Company., '22
    - Los Angeles. Judicial Candidates & Campaigns Committee., '34
    - Los Angeles Junior Chamber Of Commerce., '27
    - Los Angeles Legal Aid Society, Ltd., '30
    - Los Angeles Orphans' Home., '28
    - Los Angeles Public Library., '11
    - Los Angeles Railway Company., '06
    - Los Angeles Review., '20
    - Los Angeles Sewing Machine Company., '08; (2)
    - Los Angeles Times-Mirror Company., '29
    - Los Angeles Title Insurance Company., '22
    - Louis, E. J., '22
    - Lowe, Titus (1877 -)., '24-'31; (4)
    - Lowether, W. E., '28
    - Luckenbush, W., '14
    - Lummis, Charles F. (1859 -)., nd; (2)
    - Lund, Agnes., '31
    - Luter, John W., '27-'32; (3)
    - Lutz, Chalmer L.
    - Lyman, Clarence A., '22
    - Lyman, Edward D., '34
    - Lyon, Charles W., '27
    - [Lyons, George W.], '20
    - Lyons, Harry., '27
    - Lyons, W. E., '23
  - M - GENERAL IN. (I) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - McAdoo, Alfred H., '20-'33; (5)
    - McAdoo, William Gibbs (1863 -)., '32; (2) (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - McAllaster, Ray C., '31
    - McAvay, William., '22
    - McCallough, Phoebe M., '24
    - McCandless, F. C., '26
    - McCarthy, Neil S., '30
    - McClure, Marcus P., '21
    - McComas Dry Goods Company., '27
    - McComb, Marshall F. (1894 -)., '28-'34
    - McCormick, Paul J., '12-'24
    - McCray, C. H., '25
    - McCready, Dora A., '28
    - McCulloch, Charles E., '31
    - McDill, George W., '27-'31; (3)
    - MacDonald, Alexander (1889 -)., '24
    - McDonald, Frank A., '24
    - McDonald, George W., '22
    - McDonald, Robert W., '16
    - McEntire, Walter F., '20-'24; (4)
    - McEverlast Inc.
      - nd, 1926 - 1927, (62). (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - January - May, 1928, (51). (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - June - December, 1928, (145). (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - January - March, 1929, (166). (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - April 1 - 15, 1929, (185). (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - April 16 - 31, 1929, (207). (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - May - December, 1929, (180). (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - 1930 - 1932, (56). (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Misc. bills, receipts, printed materials, documents.
    - McGarry, D. F., '22-'24
    - McGovern, T. J., '27
    - McGroarty, John S., nd
    - McHugh, Kate A., '23
    - McInerney, Joseph., '27
    - McKee, Henry S., '24
    - McKenzie, Edwin V., '30
    - McKevitt, Hugh K., '25
    - McKim, Eiffeline., '22
    - McKinley, J. W., '27
    - McKinstry, Laura M., '27
    - McKisick, R. T., '24
    - Macklin, Robert K., '26
    - McKnight, E. L., '22
    - McLaughlin, J. B., '13
    - MacLaughlin, Leo G., '25
    - McLaughlin, R. D., '28
    - McLucas, Victor R., '26-'32; (3)
    - McMillan, J. W., '07
    - McMonigal, H. E. and Effie., '29
    - McNab, John., nd, '25; (2)
    - McNaught's Monthly., '21-'26; (2)
    - McNoble, George F., '24
    - McPherrin, Paul H., '31; (3)
    - McPherrin, Roy D., '33
    - MCRAE, FRED W., '22-'34; (14) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - MCRAE, SUE (Sister of J.W.Shenk)., '07-'25; (7) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Macrum, Charles E., '31
    - McStay, C. E., '24
    - Mahon, James E., '31
    - Maihern, Arline., '26
    - Maine, Ernest K., '25
    - H. J. Mallen and Co., Inc., '23
    - Maltman, John W., '21-'23; (4)
    - [Manders, John E.]
    - Mandil, Carmen M. de, '29
    - Marchant, Thomas W., '31-'32
    - Margales, '22
    - Marks, Samuel., '31; (2)
    - Marquardt, W. W., '01-'20
    - A. N. Marquis and Company., '25-'29
    - Marr, Ned., '34-'35; (5)
    - Marriott, Francis M. Jr., '22; (2)
    - Marsh, Norman F., '22
    - Marshall, John., '27
    - Marshall, John Murray., '13
    - Martin, Austin O., '24
    - Martin, Theodore., '24
    - Masonic Club Of Los Angeles., '26; (2)
    - Masujima, Rokuchiro., '22
    - Mather, Franklin D., '23
    - Matheson, J. L., '24
    - Mathews, William Burdette (1866 -)., '25-'31; (8)
    - Matthews, Charles., '31
    - MATTOON, EVERETT W., nd, '26-'34; (13) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Mattson, W. R.
      See Babson Institute.
  - M - GENERAL IN (II). (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Mead, William., '14
    - Meeker, Ella F., '14
    - Mehl, Katherine., nd
    - Meister, Karl P.
    - Mendocino County Bar Associations.
    - Menzies, Thomas., '22
    - Merchants and Manufacturers Association of Los Angeles., '20
    - Merchants Exchange of Oakland, California., '32
    - Merchants Trust Company., '08
    - Meredith, Alice A., '24
    - Meredith, J. M., '24
    - G. And C. Merriam Co., '25
    - Merrill, A. E., '10
    - Merrill, Richard B., '24
    - Mesmer, Joseph., '13-'30; (3)
    - Metcalf, Mr. and Mrs. R. L., '13
    - Methodist Book Concern., '33
    - Methodist Episcopal Church - Southern California Annual Conference., '24; (2)
    - Metropolitan Water District of Southern California., '34; (2)
    - Metzger, William H., '24
    - Middleton, Bessie B., '24; (2)
    - Miller, Hattie M., '23; (2)
    - Miller, John H., '22
    - Miller, Justin (1888 -)., '28
    - Miller, Kenton A., '23-'33; (6)
    - MILLIKAN, ROBERT A. (1868 -)., '31 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Minchan, Michael., '24
    - Mines, William W., '24-'33; (6)
    - Mitchell, Charles Bayard (1857 -)., '00
    - Mitchell, Irving J., nd
    - Mohr, Andrew., '10-'24; (3)
    - Mohr, W. H., '24
    - Mohr, Mrs. W. H., '22
    - Monnette, Orra Eugene (1873 -)., '13-'35; (6)
      See also BANK OF AMERICA.
    - Monroe, Charles., nd, '20-'27; (10)
    - Monroe, Henry E., '33
    - Montgomery, Charles C. (1876 -)., '24
    - Montgomery, G. D., '22
    - Montgomery, S. T., '19-'21
    - Montgomery, V., '14
    - Moodie, Joseph G., '31
    - Moore, Albert Weston (1842 -)., '24
    - Moore, Bertha C., nd
    - Moore, George Fleming., '22
    - Moore, Helene., '34; (2)
    - Moore, Homer., nd
    - Moore, Minor., '24-'31; (3)
    - Moore, Walter., '34
    - Morgan, Vincent., '31
    - Morgan, W. B.
    - Morrison, Fred. W., '33; (2)
    - Morrison, S., '22
    - [Morrison, Willis J.], '14
    - Morse, Wayne L., '33 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Morton and Pruitt., '07
    - Morton, Robert A., '31
    - Morton, Roy H., '23
    - Morton, W. Ona., '07-'13
    - Moss, Leon F., '10
    - Mott, John G., '10-'27; (4)
    - Mould, Thomas R., '20; (2)
    - Mouser, Frank H., '23
    - Movement For Better Judges., '20; (3)
    - Mueller, Oscar., nd, '30; (2)
    - Muhleman, Frank L., '24
    - Mulqueeney, P. C., '23
    - Municipal Conference of 1913., (9)
    - Municipal League Of Los Angeles., '22-'24
    - Munson, A. C., nd, '31; (2)
    - Murray, Inez., '09; (2)
    - Murray, John., '09-'14; (7)
    - Murray, Stanley., '24
    - Mutual Business Club., '31
    - Myers, Blanche., nd, '33; (3)
    - MYERS, LOUIS WESCOTT (1872 -)., nd, '24-'35; (48) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - N - GENERAL IN. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Nair, Thomas L., '26; (2)
    - Narcotic Research Association., '28
    - Nash, Paul M., '31-'32; (3)
    - Nathan-Dohrmann Company., '32
    - National Bank Of Hermosa Beach., '22
    - National Commission On Law Observance and Enforcement., '29
    - National Conference Of Jews., '33
    - National Conference Of Social Work., '29
    - National Cyclopedia of American Biography., '24
    - National Economic League., '27
    - National Geographic Society., '33
    - National Probation Association. San Francisco Committee., '29
    - National Safety League Of America., '26
    - National Sugar Company., '07
    - National Tribune., '30
    - Native Sons and Daughters of The Golden West., '31
    - Native Sons Golden State. Los Angeles Parlor., '20-'24
    - Native Sons of the Golden West., '31
    - Near East Relief., '24-'25; (3)
    - Nebraska State Society Of Southern California., '22
    - Needham, C. E., '24
    - Neisser, Otto., nd
    - Nelson, Dario H., '20-'31
    - Nelson, N. B., '25
    - Nelson, W. H., '34
    - New York Life Insurance Co., '99-'31; (7)
    - New York Times., '34
    - Newby, Nathan., '13-'23
    - Newcomer, Carl S., '24
    - Newell, R. A., '26
    - Newerf, W. D., '25
    - Newlin & Ashburn., '24
    - Newlin, Gurney E. (1880 -)., '13-'28; (4)
    - Newman, Frank J., '30-'33
    - Newman, Marjorie Hines., '23
    - Nichols, Alan., '26-'28; (6)
    - Nichols, Ernest E., '25
    - Nichols, James C., '24
    - Nichols, Walter Hammond (1866 -)., '24
    - Nickel, Helena., '07
    - Nolan, Joseph F., '30
    - North, Richard L., '21
    - North, East, West Commercial and Improvement Association., '11; (2)
    - Northern California Lawyers Golf Association., '30
    - Northrup, William M., '14
    - Northwestern Mutual Fire Association., '30
    - Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Co., '16-'29; (7)
    - Norton, Vere Radir., '30
    - Nourse, J. R., '24
  - O - GENERAL IN. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Oak Knoll District Improvement Association., '23
    - Oakland Advertising Club., '26
    - Oakland, Port Of. Board Of Port Commissioners., '30
    - Oakland Tribune., '27
    - O'Brien, Clarence A., nd
    - Occidental Life Insurance Company of California., '15-'29; (5)
    - Ocheltree, G. B., '23
    - O'Connor & Havill., '28
    - O'Connor, John Robert (1885 -)., '27
    - Odell, S. W., '16
    - Ogden, Frank M. (1895 -)., '32
    - Ohannesian, J. George., '28
    - OHIO WESLEYAN UNIVERSITY.
      - 1919 - 1930, (95). (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - 1931 - 1934, (115). (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Printed matter, forms. (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence includes letters from:
        - Beal, Bessie R.
        - Bell, Hobart.
        - Dosh, R. H.
        - Ehnes, Morris W.
        - Guthery, E. G.
        - Haggerty, William A.
        - Harris, George B.
        - Hoffman, John W.
        - Lowe, Titus.
        - Lutz, Chalmer L.
        - Meister, Karl P.
        - Monnette, Orra Eugene.
        - Shenk, John W.
        - Shipps, Herman M.
        - Soper, Edmund D.
        - Waugh, Karl T.
    - O'Kane, Frank G., '26
    - Oliver, Boyd., '27
    - Oliver, Frank S., '26-'31; (3)
    - Olney, Warren Jr. (1870 -)., '20-'29
    - Olson, Culbert Levy (1876 -)., '31
    - O'Mahoney, Joseph C., '33; (2)
    - O'Melveny, Stuart O., nd.
    - O'Melveny, Tuller, & Myers., '27-'32; (3)
    - Oneal, Louis., '34
    - O'Neill, Mrs. B., '14
    - Oneonta Club., '24-'29; (5)
    - Orange County, California. Tax Collector., '22
    - Orcutt, W. Sybil., nd, '17; (2)
    - Orr, Ethel H., '23
    - Ormsby, E. S., '13
    - Osborne, Sherrill B., '31
    - Oster, Frank F., '31; (2)
    - O'Toole, John Joseph (1872 -)., '35
    - Otto, John., '24
    - Otto, Paul J., '24-'25
    - Overton, Sherman W., '25
    - Owen, Erwin W., '24-'29; (3)
    - Owens, Timon E., '31
    - Oxnam, Garfield Bromley (1891 -)., '25
  - P - GENERAL IN. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Pace, Troy., '30-'34; (4)
    - Pacht, Isaac (1890 -)., '31
    - Pacific American Oil Company., '27-'31; (3)
    - Pacific Christian Hospital., '32
    - Pacific Gas and Electric Company., '25-'31; (4)
    - Pacific Mutual Life Insurance Company., nd
    - Padan, Franklin., '27
    - Page, Benjamin E., '25
    - Palmer, William Fleet., '30
    - Palmer, William Jackson (1890 -)., '31; (2)
    - Palomares, F. J., '13
    - Pangborn, E. J. W., '08
    - Parker, A. Junius., '22
    - [Parker, Hobart.], '24
    - Parker, Robert S., '22-'23; (3)
    - Parmele, G. H.
      See Lawyers' Cooperative Publishing Company.
    - Pasadena Bar Association., '22
    - Patrick & Company., '26
    - Patterson, Earl S., '32
    - Patton, Esther J., '23
    - Paulist Fathers., '24-'30; (3)
    - Peairs, H. A., '27
    - Peck, C. E., nd, '06-'07; (3)
    - Peck, Earl Curtis., '14
    - Peck, James E., '08-'10; (3)
    - Peck, T. C., '24
    - Peninsula Grade Crossing Conference., '29
    - People's Campaign Committee., '13
    - People's Power Bond Committee., '14-'17
    - Peoples State Bank., '22
    - Perry, Irvin David (1870 -)., '22
    - Persons, V. S., '22
    - Petermichel, J. J., '25-'27; (2)
    - Peters, H., '31
    - Petersen, Maud E., '31
    - Peterson, Henry John (1880 -)., '31
    - Petty, Don E., '33; (2)
    - Petuchi, Paul., '13
    - Phelps, William Woodward (1869 -)., nd, '27; (2)
    - Phi Delta Phi., nd, '21-'35; (6)
    - Phoenix Mutual Life Insurance Company., '78-'15
    - Pierce, Fred. E., '26
    - Pierce, Nellie Brewer., nd
    - Pike, Warren A., '25
    - Piness, George., '22-'23
    - Pitzer, Sloan., '24; (2)
    - Plummer, Robert Newton., '14
    - Polhamus, James M.
    - Pond, John E., '25-'28; (3)
    - Pope, James H., '16-'31; (6)
    - Porter, W. J., '27
    - Postal Life and Casualty Insurance Company., '30
    - Powell, Lewis M., '24-'31
    - Edward J. Power Co., Inc., '25-'26; (6)
    - Prentice-Hall Inc., nd
    - Preston, John White (1877 -)., '29
    - Preston School Of Industry., '24
    - Priaulx, Percy J., '24
    - Price, Francis (1890 -)., '34; (2)
    - Prichard, George A., '20-'31; (4)
    - Pridham, James C., '23-'24; (3)
    - Proctor, William H., '29; (2)
    - Professional Chauffers Association of California., '14
    - Progressive Country Central Committee Of Los Angeles County., '15
    - Prohibition County Central Committee Of Los Angeles County., '14; (4)
    - Protestant Legion Of America., '20
    - Pruitt, Drew., '13
    - Public Affairs Lyceum Bureau., '22; (2)
    - Public Power League., '22
    - Public Welfare Bureau., '22
    - Pullen, John Francis (1882 -)., '34; (3)
    - The Pullman Company., '27; (2)
    - Putnam, H. C., '27
  - Q - GENERAL IN. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Quillian, William Fletcher (1880 -)., '24
  - R - GENERAL IN. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Raas, Charles., '26
    - Radium Ore Revigator Company., nd
    - Rainey, Edward., '30
    - Ralston, Jackson Harvey (1857 -)., '31
    - Ramsey, G. F., '20
    - Randall, Lewis B., '24; (3)
    - Rapp and Co., Inc., '27
    - Reader Magazine., '07
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation., '33
    - Recorder Printing and Publishing Company., '25-'34; (3)
    - Redding, Mary F., '25-'33; (3)
    - Redmond, William P., '20; (2)
    - Redwine, H. G., '24-'32; (3)
    - Reed, Mrs. M. K., '24
    - Reeve, Sidney N., '21-'27; (3)
    - Religious Liberty Association., '30
    - J. C. Rendler Inc., '24
    - Repay, Theodore., '23
    - Reppy, Roy V., '24-'27
    - Republican County Central Committee Of Los Angeles County., '20-'27
    - Republican County Central Committee Of San Francisco., '34
    - Republican National Committee., '28
    - Republican State Central Committee., '18-'28; (3)
    - Reynolds, William M., '22
    - Reynolds Realty Company., '10
    - Rhea, Hannah S. G., '94-'22
    - Rheinstrom, Beatrice B., '24-'33; (4)
    - Rhoades, Jas. M., '22
    - Rhodes., nd
    - Ricca, Vetran.